

# **CARLOS HINOJOSA PINTO**

https://www.carlosh.es

# **ABOUT ME**

I am a Computer Engineering graduate from the Polytechnic University of Valencia, in Spain with more than 3 years of experience in the field. I love to learn new things and acquire new skills every day, in my free time I like to read, going to the gym and run in the mountain.

## TECH SKILLS

# Computer Languages:

- JavaScript/Typescript
- PHP
- Python
- Java
- HTML/CSS
- C/C++

# **Tecnologies:**

- React
- Node JS
- Laravel
- · Unit testing
- NextJS
- Wordpress
- Git
- Bootstrap
- MySQL

# SOFT SKILLS

- Agile methodologies
- Teamwork and collaboration
- · Goal-oriented mindset

### Languages:

- Spanish(Native)
- Inglés (B2)

### CONTACT

Telephone: (+34)664 099 349 carloshin98@gmail.com https://www.carlosh.es



### EXPERIENCE

#### **IOBUILDERS**

#### Frontend developer

September 2021 - Now

Frontend developer using **React** with **TypeScript** and testing with **Jest**. Creating a NFT Marketplace for DC COMIC in the Palm Blockchain. Working with a team in different time zones and with meetings in English.

#### **NTT DATA**

#### Frontend developer

November 2020 - September 2021

Frontend developer, using **Angular** with **Typescript** for develop a modern web application for a bank.

### **MULTISCAN TECHNOLOGIES (INTERSHIP)**

#### Software developer

January 2020 - May 2020

Software developer, I used C++ and Python for programming scanners that detects fruit and vegetables defects.

#### **ACTIVALINK (INTERSHIP)**

#### Fullstack developer

March 2019- September 2019

Fullstack developer using for backend MySQL database and React and jQuery for the frontend

### **EDUCATION**

**UPV** http://www.upv.es

**Computer Engineering Degree** 

September 2016 - June 2020

# **PROYECTS**

SELL CARS <a href="https://sell-car-carlosh.vercel.app/cars">https://sell-car-carlosh.vercel.app/cars</a>

Web to publish cars using **NextJS** with **Typescript** and **Chakra UI** for styles.

# TFG <a href="https://www.tfg.carlosh.es/app/">https://www.tfg.carlosh.es/app/</a>

Final proyect for the Computer Science Degree. This web allow you to order food from a restaurant. Done with **PHP** and **React**.

### **WEB MIGUEL PINTO** https://miguel-pinto.vercel.app/

Web made in **NextJS** and **Typescript** for the promotion of the painter Miguel Pinto.

#### **WEB BOOKS** <a href="https://www.libros.carlosh.es">https://www.libros.carlosh.es</a>

Web application to store book collections developed with Laravel.